# MANMAI PHIMSON

MANAGEMENT CONSULTANT

088-993-5557

368/72, Phetchaburi road, Ratchathewi, Bangkok, Thailand, 10400

Manmai.ps@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Over three years of consulting experiences in various industries; tourism, insurance, automotive, logistics, healthcare, asset management and SMEs. My expertise lies in statistical analysis, policy analysis, gap analysis, market research, strategic planning, and project management. I am seeking a position where I can utilize my skills to help an organization improve their operations and achieve their goals.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Chulalongkorn University

Bachelor of Economics Degree (2nd Class Honors)

Jul 2015 - Feb 2019

#### LANGUAGES

Thai (Native), English (Fluent)

#### **SKILLS**

- Proficient in statistical analysis software such as SPSS and Tableau as well as Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint
- Analytical and problem-solving skills, with the ability to develop effective solutions for complex problems
- Excellent communication and presentation skill, with the ability to translate complex technical concepts into understandable terms
- Experience working with cross-functional teams and leading projects from start to finish

# EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

#### Tutor, Chula Tutor Express

2015 - Present

8 years of experience as a Mathematics teacher for high school student

#### Volunteer teacher

Oct 2019 - Dec 2019

Developed educational quality for more than 120 students in a slum community during weekend

### Vice President 19th Econ CU First Step Camp

Jan 2018

Performed good understanding of the faculty for more than 150 students and generated inclusive opportunities, especially in the rural area

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Management Consultant**

Nov 2020 - Present

**PYI Consulting** 

- Developed five-year strategic plan for the Ministry of Tourism and Sports to promote sustainable and ecologically responsible tourism, which aims to establish Thailand as a leading global tourist destination
- Formulated five-year corporate and annual action plan, related to the State Enterprise Assessment Model (SE-AM) for the Mass Rapid Transit Authority of Thailand, that addresses the rising demand for public transportation
- Performed business plan validation for a top Vietnamese EV manufacturer to support their investment in the series D funding round for the pioneer of extreme fast charging (XFC) battery technology for EV
- Analyzed survey results by using statistical models to develop policy suggestion to reduce the debt of Small and Medium sized Enterprises (SMEs) in Thailand
- Conducted market research and foresight analysis to identify opportunities for growth of a top 5 public hospital, which supports the rising demand for the hospital
- Implemented a successful pitch a 5 MTHB project to develop a sustainable plan for the public hospital

# **Junior Business Analyst**

Jul 2020 - Oct 2020

PTTEP

Performed contract agreement review of the Gas Sales and Purchase Agreement and the Export Gas Sales Agreement ensuring PTTEP to achieve the optimum profit from the Myanmar and Zawtika Gas to Power project

#### **Business Consultant**

Feb 2020 - Jun 2020

BlueBik Group

- Developed strategy for a top 3 insurance broker company to reach 50 BTHB insurance premium target within five years from 5 BTHB
- Conducted deep dives analysis on the competitive landscape to identify the company weaknesses and developed an implementation plan for more efficient ways of working in order to address a higher number of customers